Guide to the Frank Weymouth Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Frank Weymouth papers
1900-1965
SC0018
Weymouth, Frank W. (Frank Walter), 1884-1963.
17.5 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
MEMORIAL RESOLUTION FRANK WALTER WEYMOUTH 1884-1963
Dr. Frank W. Weymouth was born June 17, 1884, in Seattle, Washington. His death in Oakland March 19, 1963, brought to an end a career of fifty three years of teaching and research. He was conducting research at the University of California School of Optometry until shortly before his death.
Dr. Weymouth's interests as an undergraduate at Stanford were almost equally divided between English Literature and Biological Sciences. He Obtained his A.B. in Zoology at Stanford in 1909 and the following year began graduate work in Physiology. He became an Assistant in 1908, received his Ph.D. in physiology in 1911 [1923] and was appointed Instructor in Physiology the following September. After spending 1912-1913 as an Assistant at Johns Hopkins, he resumed his teaching and research at Stanford. He rose through the various ranks to professorship in 1931 and becdame head of the Department of Physiology in 1938.
Dr. Weymouth's research on the campus was in the field of Physiology of the Eye, but his enduring interest in Zoology was expressed in his Summer teaching and research at the Hopkins Marine Station and in applied work during many Summer Quarters conducting fishery research for the state, federal, and British Columbia governments. His studies of the commercial crab of California began in 1911, and his later work with this species culminated in his drafting the fishery regulations for the State Legislature that are still in effect.
An abiding interest in people and their welfare was not limited to his contacts with students; he was a champion of civil rights, an active worker with minority groups. Emeritus status and retirement were not synonymous in Frank Weymouth's view: shortly after he attained emeritus rank at Stanford, he began a new teaching and research career at the Los Angeles College of Optometry. He was a member of the faculty of that school until the rule of age again resulted in his becoming Professor Emeritus of the Log Angeles College of Optometry in 1960.
He is remembered by his few remaining colleagues, his many students and friends at Stanford and elsewhere as a particularly happy bridge between the biological-humanistic traditions of Dr. Jordan and the solid role of physiology in modern medical education. Surely nothing but devotion to his school and to people could account for fifteen years of service as Chairman of the Committee on Admissions to the School of Medicine.
Dr. Weymouth is survived by a large family with origins in two marriages. We extend our deepest sympathy to his wife, the former Mary Balsbaugh Dierup, his two daughters, Mrs. Alice Kunets and Mrs. Anne Dierup, both of Berkeley, to his son, Dr. John Weymouth of the faculty of the University of Nebraska, his stepson, Torben Dierup of Berkeley, his stepdaughter, Mrs. Mary Chernoff of Berkeley, and ten grandchildren and one greatgrandchild.
Respectfully submitted to the Academic Council,
J. M. Crismon, Chairman
R. Grant
V. Twitty
Collection Contents
- Papers
  - Correspondence and Notes
    - Vision of the aging (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Visual accuity (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Notes on the physiology of the eye (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Cornea (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Spectroscope (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Visual data mixed (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Relative growth of the eye (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Paper on myopia (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Williams and Wilkin Publishers (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Corresp. on Textbook of Physiology (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Fulton Howell Television Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Research Notes (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Misc. Eye Notes some lectures (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Saunders Corresp. On Eye (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Syllabus on the Eye (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Misc. Eye Not es some lecturec (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Eye minimum visible (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Eye (Unsorted notes) (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Eye (Mixed notes) (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Eye muscle balance demonst. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Eye problems sample (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Sparrows cornea (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Adaptation and vitamin E deficiency (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Eye suggestions, Calvin (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - American Academy of Optometry (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Chick pupil (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Binocular vision, moving target (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - History of Vision Lab at Stanford (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Crozier (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Eye Notes (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Eye, Calvin rod free (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Eye, coated lenses (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Eye experiments (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Lecture notes and misc. notes (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Sampling problems in opthamology (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Talk found in folder w/1928 material (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Talk on eye (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Eye misc. correspondence (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Knudsen correspondence (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Student correspondence - Craig Taylor (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Student - Drach (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Monroe Hirsch, correspondence (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Monroe Hirsch, corresp. Eye (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Borden stereoscope (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Misc. correspondence (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Biometrics meeting (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Biometric outline (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Biometrics corresp. (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Rashevsky's book (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - The evolution of a lesson in biometry (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Biometry, rainfall at Mountain View (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Students, medical school (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Admissions (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Corresp. Shuster (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Shelokov, corresp. (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Education, corresp. (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Stanford Memorials (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Articles on optometry (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Diploma, MA/Stanford (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Corresp. Smithsonian (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Employment and Beraueu of fisheries (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Statistics, Medical School (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Statistics (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Lectures and Statistics (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Moments (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Statistics and Corresp. (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Pugettia Producta (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - News clippings (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Family pictures (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Family clippings (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Family documents (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Lay sermon (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Prof. of German, Charley Reining (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Articles and Dissertations
    - Stanford dissertations and articles by Weymouth (Box 2)
      Not copies of Weymouth's own thesis and dissertation
  - Notebooks of Weymouth
    - Notebooks of Weymouth (10) (Box 3)
  - Syllabus' of classes taught by Weymouth
    - Syllabus' of classes taught by Weymouth (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, Documents and Notes
    - Diplomas (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Corresp., OPJ (Jenkins) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Stanford notebook (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Tape - memorial service for Weymouth (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Family documents (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Alumni documents (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Jour. of the Calif. Optometry Assoc. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Bio. on Weymouth (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Amer. J. of Optometry (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Corresp. To Mrs. T. Deirup (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Frank Weymouth Memorial (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Bulletin of Lectures (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper clipping (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Dates of family (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Personal, biography (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - American Historical Co. Corresp. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Medical class pictures (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Memorials and newsclippings (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Bibliography of F. W. Weymouth (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Personal data (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Employment record at Stanford (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Misc. speeches (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence and Notebooks
    - A poem (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Corres. Kirby Page (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Accident saved by dates (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Biography (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, personal unsorted (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Corresp. 1922 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Corresp. Misc. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Memorial letters about Frank W. Weymouth (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Consultant case, vignette (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Corresp. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - News clippings (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Unitarian, corresp. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Employment, corresp. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Letter files, FWW (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Mixed corresp. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Letters mostly biographic (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Unsorted letters (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - English, 1906-1907 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Notebook (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Verse (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Worse (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Book review (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence
    - Palo Alto tree, history (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Margaret Miller (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Alice Weymouth (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. F. W. Weymouth Corresp. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Proof of birth paper (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - The Tahoma (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Pageant Pictures (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Mostly prose (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Prose (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, clams
    - Annual report 1929 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Tirela young (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Kirkak (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Oil pollution, S.F. Bay (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Runner upon Piamo clam (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Growth symposium (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Parts and cycles of growth (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Kleifer (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Growth (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Clam growth (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Discussion of compensatory growth (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Clam razor growth (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Body size metabolism etc (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Animals, metabolism (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Discarded from growth paper (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Oscar W. Richards (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Clam, correspondence (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Clam growth correspondence (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Tivela general talk, clam (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Drawings clam (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Coefficient of variability (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Copy of articles for publication (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Spawning season (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Clam (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence on clams
    - Clam (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Tirela adult ring and total size (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Razor clam (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Systematic razor clam (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Curve fitting (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - _ Adult (Mexico) (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 1919 variations _ (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Length/weight (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Ring I, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Length ring I, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Siliqua (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Variability D. etc. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Rubour growth (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Form summary - relative growth (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Growth (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Growth and Metabolism (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Growth talk Berkeley, Pacific Grove, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Handbook of biological data (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Journal club data records (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Journal club growth (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Respiratory movements and regulation (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Group II eye movements (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Huxley separates (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Growth and Metabolism (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Corres. Physiology (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Physiology B _ (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Mixed observation (own) (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence and Notes, Physiology
    - Cutaneous receptors tempt. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Temperature (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Unsorted notes and suggestions (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Physiology 155 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Harvard apparatus (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Admission (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Nerve conductors (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Physiology introduction (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Physiology 153 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Outline of lectures (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Physiology 205 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Weymouth criticisms (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Physiology class (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Example of exam questions (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Physiology 1918 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Hamilton correspondence (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Physiology Stanford (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Verse duplicates (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Poetry saved (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Notebook (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Phi Betta Kappa 1912 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Historical correspondence on chapter "Eye" (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, and Misc.
    - Colonial Play (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - El Profeta own copy (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Alice Weymouth "Palo Alto Tree" (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Addis (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Talk 1948 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Academic freedom (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Political mis. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Medical (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Political talks (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Citizens committee (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Pauling Dinner (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Investigative committee (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Alice J. Weymouth (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Letters FWW to Mary (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Family letter 1927 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Notes on "Thot" (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Notes on philosophy (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Phsiology class notes (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Physiology (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Blom Lecture notes (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Datebooks, Corresp., Textbooks
    - Elements of Physiology by Weymouth (Box 12)
    - Primary Lessons in Human Physiology by Weymouth (Box 12)
    - Advanced Lessons in human Physiology by Weymouth (Box 12)
    - Physiology and Hygiene by Weymouth (Box 12)
    - Notebook on Biometry (Box 12)
    - Notebook on Physiology 153 (Box 12)
    - Publications by the Institute of Marine Science (Box 12)
  - Books and articles
    - Autographed articles (Box 13)
    - Autograph book (Box 13)
    - Articles by Stanford profs. (Box 13)
  - Lecture notes
    - 2 file Drawers (Box 13)
  - Correspondence and notes on fish and shrimp
    - Shrimp corresp. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Shrimp paper (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Shrimp (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Shrimp corresp. Unsorted (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Fisheries unsorted corresp. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - New Orleans corresp. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Shrimp notes (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Shrimp report (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Fisheries unsorted corresp. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Fisheries unsorted corresp. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Fisheries unsorted corresp. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - More fisheries corresp. Un-sorted (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Cockle growth paper (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Crab corresp. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence and notes on Crabs
    - Physiology, Pacific Grove (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Fisheres reading lists (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Talk on Alaska (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Donald MacKay (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Corresp. Crab metabolism (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Crab paper (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Crabs (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Crab metabolism (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Crab poem (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Pugettia producta (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Pugettia producta, summer 39 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Imaginal molt (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Molting records not complete (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Size at maturity (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Pugettia producta summer 38 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Mackay (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Key to Monterey Brachyura (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Key to Monterey Brachyura (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Key to Monterey Brachyura (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Clam (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Corresp. Fisheries (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Corresp. Willis Rich (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Mussell poisoning (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Zoo field trips (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Notebook on containing species studies (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Slugs corresp. (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Mixed (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Phd. Candidate reading list (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - "The inheritance of acquired Characteristics" (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Man as a unique organism (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Diagram of tuber species (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - History of cell theory (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Notes on Greek Science (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Graphs for reports (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Physiology 253 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, clams, eye and notes on the eye
    - Corresp. Re clams (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Eye (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Capacities of retina (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Exercie in man (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Anisooxypia (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Various notes on the eye (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Eye problem notes (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Eye notes and lecture (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Convergence (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Vision (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Flimmerskotom (FWW) (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Binocular vision (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Notes on refraction (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - MS and notes (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Scientific material "Vision of Aging Parent" (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Notes on squint (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Zajackowska (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Notes on separate eye (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Class experiments, eye (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Myopia (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Lens in congenital cataract (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Talks (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Lenses (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, In (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, In (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, In (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Out (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Photographs of equipment (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Vision (Eye) studies (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Vision (Eye) studies (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Physiology I, 1907-1909 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Physiology V (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Physiology VI, lecture notes (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Vision (Eye) studies (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Vision (Eye) studies (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Vision (Eye) studies (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Physiology 105 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Physiology 105 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Biometry 176 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Thesis on Bullfrog (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Weymouth lecture notes (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, papers and drawings on the Crab (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and papers on Clams and Mussels (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and papers on Clams and Mussels (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous papers (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous papers (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Grade Reports, 1893-1905 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Commencement programs (Aberdeen and Tacoma schools) (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Misc. school papers (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Grammar school compositions (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Grammar school notebook (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Copybooks (grammar school) (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Pressed flowers in composition book (Tacoma) (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Botany notebook, high school (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Botany notebook, high school (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Loose items from botany notebook (in folder 9) (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Physical geography notebook, Tacoma High School (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Physical geography notebook, Tacoma High School (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Poetry notebook, ca. 1904 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Tahoma, student publication, 1904-1905 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Zoology notebook, Tacoma High School (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - LSJU, Recommendation for Exemption from Entrance Examinations for Frank W. Weymouth, June 1905 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Apparatus notes (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Comparative anatomy notebook (Prof. Snyder), with drawings (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Notebook on crabs, with photographs (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Notebook on crustacea, with photograph and drawings (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Embryology drawings (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - English notes, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - English 6, course materials and notes, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Histology 9, ca. 1910 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Drawings of the human brain (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Invertebrates, drawings and notes, 1907 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Invertebrate embryology (Prof. Heath), 1909 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Neurology, 1909, course materials, tests, drawings (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Physiology 2 and 3, 1906 - 1907, notes and charts (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Zoology I (Prof. Price), notes and drawings (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Diary, 1901 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Diary, 1906 Feb. - May (with account of earthquake) (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous non-school item: several booklets on health by Dr. Edward B. Warman; postcard to Weymouth (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence re LACO (Box 24)
  - Publications by others (Box 25)